animestatic.com 2013-12-01

# Privacy Policy | Watch Anime Online - English Dubbed Anime - Free Anime Episodes

Game advertisements by [Game Advertising Online](http://www.game-advertising-online.com) require iframes.

Animestatic has made our Youtube video featuring pictures of our loyal fans! **[WATCH IT HERE](http://www.animestatic.org/news/animestatic-youtube-video/)**! 

**What information does Animestatic collect?**

Protecting the privacy of Animestatic.com’s visitors is very important to us.  
We here at Animestatic.com are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Animestatic.com and its staff will never ask for any personal information (other than, but not limited to, username/email when leaving a comment. You can, however, leave a completely anonymous username/email).

**Video Disclaimer**  
No video content is held on our servers and we, along with our staff, are in no way affiliated with the video content. The video content that is displayed originates from online video streaming websites, such as, but not limited to Dailymotion, Yourupload, MyspaceTV, Veoh, Putlocker, etc.

**Copyright Infringement**  
_In case of copyright infringement, please directly contact the responsible parties._  
Animestatic.Com operates as an index and database of Anime content found publicly available on the internet, in principle conducting in the same way as any of the large search engines, such as Google, Bing and Yahoo. However, Animestatic.Com and its staff strongly believe in the protection of intellectual property and would be willing to assist when possible and applicable. If you believe a link should be removed from the website, and have already contacted the responsible parties regarding the video(s), then please contact us directly.

Users who upload to the video streaming websites mentioned above agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts. Animestatic.Com does not accept responsibility for content hosted on third party websites, nor do we upload videos ourselves or encourage others to do so. The videos are streamed directly from the third-party video sharing services.

**Does Animestatic.Com use cookies?**  
As most websites on the internet, yes. For those of you who are unaware, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Animestatic.Com use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools for users in the future.

**Advertising**  
Animestatic.Com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may compile data (not including any personal information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
Animestatic.Com reserves the right to make any changes to our Privacy Policy, at any time. If and when we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, with an update that can be viewed site-wide.

Game advertisements by [Game Advertising Online](http://www.game-advertising-online.com) require iframes.

**Frequently Asked Questions**

**Question:** When I load the page, there aren't any videos being displayed. What happened?

**Answer:** _Every episode has videos with multiple [often 5+] mirrors. If, after refreshing the page, there are still no videos, please try clearing your cache, and flushing your DNS._

\--------------------

**Question:** The video is loading slow/not loading.

**Answer:** _That's either a connection problem on your end, or the source website is loading slow. If the video is taking too long to load, simply try a mirror, as each mirror is a different source website. If the video isn't loading at all, or is coming up with an error, please report it so we can look into it further._

\--------------------

**Question:** I keep getting a "You have watched 72 minutes of video" message. What does it mean?

**Answer:** _If you want to bypass the Megavideo time limit, then you should invest in a Megavideo Premium account. Either that, or swap to another mirror, watch an hour of video on another source, then go back to Megavideo. There will always be mirrors for episodes, so you'll always have another source to avoid the 72 minute cap._
